

PROFILE

I'm a React front-end developer with 2 years of experience building user interfaces and web applications. and I have strong skills in React, Next.js, and I'm proficient in integrating rest-ful APIs. I have a passion for building user-friendly interfaces and a deep understanding of browser compatibility and optimization techniques. I also excellent communication and problem-solving abilities. experience and expertise make me a valuable addition to any development team looking to create engaging and interactive web applications using modern front-end technologies.

EXPERTISE

- React js
- Next js
- Redux toolkit
- Git
- TypeScript
- Html, Css, Javascript
- Tailwind css
- bootstrap
- Mantine
- Formik, yup
- Axios

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH URDU

khalil **ahmed**

React developer

↓ +923070599766

panhwarkhalilahmed@gmail.com

panhwarkhalilahmed@gmail.com

EXPERIENCES

Newtown IT Services , <u>Australia</u> | Dec 2022- continue React, Nextjs developer

• worked on multiple project with Nextjs, and React.js.

Poulta | Jan 2022- dec 2022 React, Next js developer

 worked on media management and user management app with Next js , tailwind css, redux toolkit, and formik.

Digiventic | Jun 2021- dec 2021 Html, css, and js developer

worked as a frontend developer on, Html, CSS, and javascript

PROJECTS

Occsaviors - nft and cripto project

Substances study platform

devices management admin panel

EDUCATION

Web development | 2022/03 - 2022/06 Hidya institute of science & technology

Bachelor of computer science | 2018 - 2021 University of Sindh Jamshoro

Intermediate | 2015 - 2017 Boys degree college Bhansayedabad